https://www.sprtool.com/privacy-policy/

OEM ProductsLine Boring Machines4-14 ET Line Boring Machine4-14 HD Line Boring Machine4-14 Pro MK3Cadet12-36 Line Boring Machine2000 & 2500 Boring BarBore WeldersSmart Weld BW-830Easy Weld BW-612Large Bore BW-1200Linear MillsExchanger MillsRotary MillsOD Mount Flange FacersID Mount Flange FacersInLine Turning LathesIsolation & Weld TestingSmall BoreStandardGripper Type ToolsPipe BevelersCustom EngineeringTrainingRentalsPipe Cutting & BevelingID Mount Beveling ToolSplit FrameOD Mount Flange FacersIsolation & Weld TestingSmall BoreStandard BoreGripper Type ToolsLinear MillsExchanger MillsRotary MillsLine Boring Machines4-14 ET Line Boring Machine4-14 HD Line Boring Machine4-14 Pro MK3Cadet12-36 Line Boring Machine2000 & 2500 Boring BarBore WeldersSmart Weld BW-830Easy Weld BW-612Large Bore BW-1200Tensioning & BoltingHydraulic TensionerPneumatic Torque GunHydraulic Torque WrenchPortable DrillsInline Turning LathesID Mount Flange FacersTrainingPrecision Grinding & ToolingID MountClamshellsSquaring ToolsNewsAbout UsContact UsLocations & DealersGet a QuoteSuperior Plant Rentals (SPR) Privacy PolicyYour privacy is important to Superior (“SPR” or “we”) as is your trust in SPR’s products and services. We believe in transparency and we are committed to being upfront about our privacy practices, including how we treat your personal information. This policy explains our privacy practices for sprtool.com (“the Site”).Types of Data We CollectWe collect information. For example, if you sign up for a mailing list, request a quote, or enter a promotion, you may be asked to provide your name, company name, address, email, and cell phone number.We collect information you submit or post. We collect information that you post in a public space on the Site. We also collect information when you contact us or when you apply for a job.We collect usage information. We may collect information about the browser you are using. We might look at what site you came from or what site you visit when you leave the SPR Site. If you are using a mobile app, we may collect location information, including your precise location, if you have enabled location services in your device settings. We may also collect device identifiers.Purpose for Collecting DataCustomer Service. We use your personal data for customer service purposes, including responding to your inquiries. This typically requires the use of certain personal contact information and information regarding the reason for your inquiry (i.e. obtaining a quote, technical issue, product question/complaint, general question, etc.).Contests, Marketing, and Other Promotions. With your consent (where required), we use your personal data to provide you with information about goods or services (i.e. marketing communications, campaigns, or promotions). This can be done via means such as emails, ads, SMS, phone calls, and postal mailing to the extent permitted by applicable laws. Some of our campaigns and promotions are run on social networks. The use of your personal data is voluntary, which means that you can oppose (or withdraw your consent in certain countries) to the processing of your personal data for these purposes. For detailed information on how to modify your preferences about marketing communications, please see Section 7 below. For more information about our contests and other promotions, please see the official rules or details posted with each contest/promotion.Data Storage, Security and AccessWe take steps to protect your personal information from unauthorized access and against unlawful process, accidental loss, destruction, and damage. We will only keep your personal information for as long as we reasonably require. Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure and, although we will take steps to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information via the Site; any transmission is therefore at your own risk.California Privacy PolicyIf you are a California resident you have the right to request information from SPR regarding the manner in which we share certain categories of your personal information with third parties, for the third parties direct marketing purposes. California law provides that you have the right to submit a request to SPR at its designated address and receive the following information:The categories of information SPR disclosed to third parties’ direct marketing purposes during the preceding calendar year and,The names and addresses of the parties that received such information, or if the nature of their business cannot be determined from the name, then examples of the products or services marketed.You are entitled to receive a copy of this information in a standardized format and the information will not be specific to you individually. You may make such a request by using the information located in Section 7.CookiesCookies are pieces of data that sites and services can set on your browser or device that can be read on future visits. We may use third party website analytics tools such as Google Analytics on our Site that employ cookies to collect certain information concerning your use of our services. However, you can disable cookies by changing your browser settings. Further information about the procedure to follow in order to disable cookies can be found on your Internet browser provider’s website via your help screen.Changes to Our Privacy NoticeWe reserve the right to amend this privacy notice at our discretion and at any time. When we make material changes to this privacy notice, we will notify you by email or through a notice on our website homepage.Contact InformationIf you have any questions or comments about this notice, our privacy statement, the ways in which we collect and use your personal information, or your choices and rights regarding such use, please do not hesitate to contact us at:Phone: 833.447.3777 Website: www.sprtool.com Email: info@sprtool.com
